Contact

info@behealthykc.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sammicreach (LinkedIn)

www.behealthykc.com (Company)

Top Skills

Leadership

Education

Teamwork

Sammi Creach

Passionate leader that focuses on mindset and wellness to help others create success in life and business

Kearney, Missouri

Summary

Being employed can feel secure. It also leads to a lack of fulfillment, missed purpose, and no challenge. There was no passion behind what I was doing. My life got planned around my work schedule. I spent countless hours of life just commuting to work. Vacation was at the mercy of my boss. I was so tired and uninspired, I couldn't even enjoy time off.

I was paycheck to paycheck. Bare minimums were getting paid just to stay current. I was barely able to pay my student loans I took out to get my two Masters degrees. What if there was an emergency? It was all so stressful.

Stress affected my health. My habits were a pot of coffee each morning, then afternoon a pop and candy. I took medicine for my daily headaches, my stomach was constantly in knots, I had stomach issues from food allergies and intolerances (made worse with stress), and seasonal allergies were year-round it seemed. My mentality suffered too. I was in survival mode, lived with regret, was dull with no vitality, and just succumbed to the fact that "this was going to be my life".

Guess what? Things can change! Since I took the leap and embraced being my own boss, I have found my calling. My life is much more purposeful, and I am more fulfilled. My life and my impact has meaning. My confidence has grown significantly. I no longer work in the nursing field, and in addition "retired" my husband from his corporate job so that he can chase HIS dreams. Our family can travel for weeks at a time. Now we plan work around our vacations! Our biggest value is in experiences with our children. I picked a business model that focuses on residual income. With this, we are able to put into savings and retirement. We are on a path to being completely debt free!

I started out as just wanting to do this for me, to it growing into something I wanted to do to help my family. Now that I've reached that goal, my MISSION is to empower others to regain their vitality and create the life they've envisioned having.

Experience

Be Healthy KC, LLC Independent Business Owner May 2013 - Present (7 years 3 months) United States

healthcare facility RN, MSN, MBA May 2007 - Present (13 years 3 months)

Education

Shaw Academy
Diploma, Personal Nutrition · (2018 - 2018)

University of Mary
MSN, Administration · (2010 - 2011)

University of Mary

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Healthcare (2010 - 2011)

Park University

ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2006 - 2007)